<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'>
	<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic</id>
	<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
	<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
	<title type='text'>sessions</title>
	<link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ'/>
	<link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic'/>
	<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic'/>
	<author>
		<name>roman.nurik</name>
		<email>roman.nurik@gmail.com</email>
	</author>
	<openSearch:totalResults>108</openSearch:totalResults>
	<openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cpzh4</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 2</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 8, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: 3D Graphics on Android: Lessons learned from Google Body, sessiontags: Android, OpenGL, Google Body, sessionspeakers: Nico Weber, sessionabstract: Google originally built Google Body, a 3D application that renders the human body in incredible detail, for WebGL-capable browsers running on high-end bPCs.  To bring the app to Android at a high resolution and frame rate, Nico Weber and Won Chun had a close encounter with Android's graphics stack.  In this session Nico will present their findings as best practices for high-end 3D graphics using OpenGL ES 2.0 on Android.  The covered topics range from getting accelerated pixels on the screen to fast resource loading, performance guidelines, texture compression, mipmapping, recommended vertex attribute formats, and shader handling. The talk also touches on related topics such as SDK vs NDK, picking, and resource loading., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/N2j99, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/N2j99, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: 3d-graphics-android, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YLVbLVtjDDw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cpzh4'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cre1l</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 3</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 9, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Accelerated Android Rendering, sessiontags: Android, Honeycomb, UI, sessionspeakers: Romain Guy, Chet Haase, sessionabstract: Android 3.0 introduced a new hardware accelerated 2D rendering pipeline. In this talk, you will be introduced to the overall graphics architecture of the Android platform and get acquainted with the various rendering APIs at your disposal. You will learn how to choose the one that best fits your application. This talk will also deliver tips and tricks on how to use the new hardware accelerated pipeline to its full potential., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ybXAM, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ybXAM, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: accelerated-android-rendering, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v9S5EO7CLjo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cre1l'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/chk2m</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 4</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 9, sessionproduct:  Android, Google Cloud, GPE, ADT , sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Android + App Engine: A Developer's Dream Combination   , sessiontags: Android, App Engine, Cloud, Eclipse, Java, ADT, GPE, , sessionspeakers: Xavier Ducrohet, Brad Abrams, sessionabstract: This talk will introduce App Engine Tooling for Android.  A complete set of Eclipse-based Java development tools for building Android applications that are backed by App Engine.  With these tools developers can focus on building fantastic Android applications using common tools and techniques that span the client and server parts of the application AND make it extremely simple to deploy the server side to App Engine. This talk walks through building a fantastic cloud based android application., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/XfByq, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/XfByq, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: android-app-engine-dream, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M7SxNNC429U</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/chk2m'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ciyn3</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 5</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Android Development Tools, sessiontags: Android, Tools, SDK, sessionspeakers: Xavier Ducrohet, Tor Norbye, sessionabstract: This talk provides an in-depth look at the Android development tools, along with tips &amp; tricks for getting the most out of them. From project support, to source editing and visual editors, to emulator execution and debugging and profiling, this talk will help you get more productive with Android development. The main focus is on Eclipse, but we will discuss other complementary tools as well. This is a demo-oriented talk, and our goal is to show the available features, and how they fit into the workflow., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/22oSz, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/22oSz, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: android-development-tools, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oq05KqjXTvs</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ciyn3'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ckd7g</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 6</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Android Market for Developers, sessiontags: Android, Android Market, sessionspeakers: Eric Chu, sessionabstract: There are few things developers care more about than Android Market and, during the year since Google IO 2010, we have been investing huge amounts of efforts in expanding and improving it.  This presentation walks through what's new, with a particular focus on where developers can take action to improve their apps' Market performance., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ylfxw, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ylfxw, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: android-market-for-developers, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GxU8N21wfrM</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ckd7g'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/clrrx</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 7</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: Android Protips: Advanced Topics for Expert Android App Developers, sessiontags: Android, user experience, SDK, sessionspeakers: Reto Meier, sessionabstract: Writing an app is easy, but with 100k competitors you need to do better than launch and cross your fingers. I'll demonstrate how to use advanced Android techniques to take a good app and transform it into a polished product. Features advanced coding tips &amp; tricks, design and implementation patterns, and insight into some of the lesser known API features. This is an advanced session designed to help experienced developers.
, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/TxPvB, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/TxPvB, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: android-protips, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=twmuBbC_oB8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/clrrx'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cztg3</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 8</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 9, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Best Practices for Accessing Google APIs on Android, sessiontags: Google APIs, Java, Android, sessionspeakers: Yaniv Inbar, sessionabstract: Integration with Google APIs (such as Buzz, Latitude and Translate) can enrich many Android applications. In this session, we will demonstrate how to do so easily, efficiently and securely using the Google API Client for Java. We’ll walk you through how to authenticate for the APIs using AccountManager, how to reduce the client library size and several other Android-specific optimizations., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/lLBGg, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/lLBGg, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: best-practices-google-apis-android, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9fBcrzA-hWY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cztg3'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d180g</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 9</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 8, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Bringing C and C++ Games to Android, sessionspeakers: Ian Ni-Lewis, Dan Galpin, sessionabstract: Want to make great Android games, but you're not a Java programmer? This talk is for you. Android supports a toolchain for building applications in C/C++. In December 2010 it got a makeover specifically aimed at making life better for game developers. This presentation gives an introduction to Android programming in C/C++, covers what's new and improved since last year, and shows best practices for building and debugging games with the NDK., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/067wb, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/067wb, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: bringing-c-cpp-games-android, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5yorhsSPFG4</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d180g'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cssly</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 10</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 8, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Building Aggressively Compatible Android Games, sessiontags: Gaming, NDK, Java, sessionspeakers: Chris Pruett, sessionabstract: There are a lot of Android phones out there, but by abiding to a few key rules it is possible to develop a single binary that runs on all of them. This session will explain how to approach device diversity and build aggressively compatible Android games., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/XFzv0, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/XFzv0, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: aggressively-compatible-games-android, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cdvaPyq_eBU</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cssly'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cu76f</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 11</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Google TV, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Building Android Apps for Google TV, sessiontags: TV, Android, Java, sessionspeakers: Jason Bayer, Christian Kurzke, sessionabstract: Learn how to create new apps or enhance existing Android apps for Google TV. Session includes an overview of the platform, best practices, demos, and discussion about the fantastic opportunities Google TV creates for developers., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ZU0ew, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ZU0ew, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: building-android-apps-google-tv, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CxLL-sR6XfM</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cu76f'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cvlqs</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 12</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Designing and Implementing Android UIs for Phones and Tablets, sessiontags: Android, user experience, design, sessionspeakers: Roman Nurik, Adam Powell, Richard Fulcher, Christian Robertson, Matias Duarte , sessionabstract: There are a large number of Android tablet devices starting to ship. This session discusses the new APIs and tools available to developers for use in constructing apps that work well on them, and provides guidance on creating good user experience for users of these devices., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/Srkzm, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/Srkzm, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: designing-android-uis, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WGIU2JX1U5Y</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cvlqs'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cx0b9</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 13</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Mobile monetization, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Don’t just build a mobile app. Build a business., sessiontags: mobile, monetization, ads, AdMob, Android, SDK, sessionspeakers: Wayne Pan, sessionabstract: Learn how to build a business on mobile apps so you can quit your day job. Walk away with an understanding of app business basics and how to use house ads for app promotion, mediation to optimize in-app advertising revenues and analytics to measure real ROI., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/QK7t7, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/QK7t7, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: dont-just-build-mobile-app, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wHAR46DT8ok</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/cx0b9'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d9ney</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 14</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 8, sessionproduct: Android,App Engine, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Evading Pirates and Stopping Vampires using License Verification Library, In-App Billing, and App Engine, sessiontags: Gaming, App Engine, Cloud, Security, sessionspeakers: Dan Galpin, Trevor Johns, sessionabstract: This session talks about best practices for using the License Verification Library and In-App Purchases on Android Market. It also explains how to integrate a server-side component for license validation and content delivery, describing the reference implementation that we built using App Engine., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/pbHro, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/pbHro, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: evading-pirates-stopping-vampires, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TnSNCXR9fbY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d9ney'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/db1zf</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 15</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Fireside Chat with the Android Team, sessiontags: Android, sessionspeakers: Dan Bornstein, Debajit Ghosh, Dave Sparks, Xavier Ducrohet, Jeff Hamilton, Andrew Stadler, Dan Morrill, Dianne Hackborn, Rebecca Schultz Zavin, Chris DiBona, Ficus Kirkpatrick, sessionabstract: Join us for an informal developer-oriented discussion of what's been going on in the world of Android., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ESrBI, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ESrBI, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: fireside-chat-android, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gfiYUL2exT8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/db1zf'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dcgjs</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 16</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Honeycomb Highlights, sessiontags: Android, Honeycomb , sessionspeakers: Romain Guy, Chet Haase, sessionabstract: Android's "Honeycomb" release includes a large number of new features, capabilities, and APIs to access them.  This session gives a high-level view of everything that's new, with special focus on how this affects developers' lives and what they should be paying attention to., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/UkNLB, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/UkNLB, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: honeycomb-highlights, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sTx-5CGDvM8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dcgjs'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ddv49</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 17</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: How to NFC, sessionspeakers: Nick Pelly, Jeff Hamilton, sessionabstract: Gingerbread brings a comprehensive NFC reader/writer API, and some modest but surprisingly powerful P2P support. Come hear why you should care about NFC technology, what kinds of applications are possible right now, and best practices for deployment., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/nqTfS, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/nqTfS, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: how-to-nfc, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=49L7z3rxz4Q</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ddv49'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d415a</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 18</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 9, sessionproduct: Android / HTML5, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: HTML5 versus Android: Apps or Web for Mobile Development?, sessiontags: Android, Mobile, HTML5, sessionspeakers: Reto Meier, Michael Mahemoff, sessionabstract: Native apps or mobile web? It's often a hard choice when deciding where to invest your mobile development resources. While the mobile web continues to grow, native apps and App Stores are incredibly popular. We will present both perspectives in an app development smackdown., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/44qLB, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/44qLB, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: html5-versus-android-apps-or-web, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4f2Zky_YyyQ</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d415a'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d5fpr</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 19</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 9, sessionproduct: Android, Accessibility, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Leveraging Android Accessibility APIs To Create An Accessible Experience, sessiontags: android, eyesfree, access, sessionspeakers: Charles Chen, T.V. Raman, Tim Credo, sessionabstract: The Android framework includes a set of easy-to-use APIs that enables the creation of third-party accessibility services such as screenreaders for the blind. In this talk, we'll give an overview of the Accessibility API, describe some of the most widely used services, and explain how to fully unlock the  accessibility potential of the Android platform., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/TibKa, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/TibKa, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: leveraging-android-accessibility, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BPXqsPeCneA</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d5fpr'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d6ua4</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 20</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 9, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: Memory management for Android apps, sessionspeakers: Patrick Dubroy, sessionabstract: Android apps have more memory available to them than ever before, but are you sure you're using it wisely? This talk will cover the memory management changes in Gingerbread and Honeycomb (concurrent GC, heap-allocated bitmaps, "largeHeap" option) and explore tools and techniques for profiling the memory usage of Android apps., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/hFbB2, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/hFbB2, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: memory-management-android, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_CruQY55HOk</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d6ua4'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d88ul</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 21</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 9, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Optimizing Android Apps with Google Analytics, sessionspeakers: Nick Mihailovski, Philip Mui, Jim Cotugno, sessionabstract: Thousands of apps have taken advantage of Google Analytics' native Android tracking capabilities to improve the adoption and usability  of Andriod Apps. This session covers best practices for tracking apps on mobile, TV and other devices. We'll also show you how to gain actionable insights from new tracking and reporting capabilities., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/0XVsh, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/0XVsh, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: optimizing-android-apps-analytics, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DTcZPE8Twpg</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/d88ul'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dkvya</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 22</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 11, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Taking Android to Work, sessionspeakers: Fred Chung, Andrew Stadler, Gabriel Cohen, sessionabstract: More and more people are bringing Android devices into enterprise environments.  This talk will cover general enterprise adoption considerations and related Android features.  We will also provide an overview of security issues, managed internal app development, corporate app directories, and an in-depth look at a sample implementation of device management policies.  , sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/xG0lX, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/xG0lX, sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: taking-android-to-work, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ScW4zSeexvo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dkvya'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dmair</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 23</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Building Enterprise Applications on App Engine, sessiontags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Chris Schalk, Greg Dalesandre, sessionabstract: In its three short year history, Google App Engine has evolved from its grass roots developer origins to a technology used more and more by global businesses. This session will review App Engine’s history and explain how it will be continuing to evolve to serve an increasing Enterprise audience. Specific technical milestones will be cited along with a detailed discussion on the future of App Engine will be discussed. Several App Engine business partners will also be highlighted and will be on stage to explain how they’ve used App Engine in a business context and how they see using App Engine in the future., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ZQp2V, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ZQp2V, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: building-enterprise-apps, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Dwf3rtucXY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dmair'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dnp34</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 24</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, Cloud Storage, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Coding For The Cloud: How We Write Enterprise Apps for Google on App Engine, sessiontags: App Engine, Tech Talk, Development, Cloud, sessionspeakers: Ben Fried, Justin McWilliams, Eric Schoeffler, Justin Fagnani, sessionabstract: Google's IT department builds the enterprise apps that run Google as a company. Come hear Google's CIO and engineers talk about what they've built and learn the tips, techniques and software design patterns that you can use to build applications on App Engine., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/MY5kv, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/MY5kv, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: coding-for-cloud, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wWhd9ZwvCyw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dnp34'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dp3nl</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 25</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Fireside Chat with the App Engine Team, sessiontags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Max Ross, Alon Levi, Sean Lynch, Greg Dalesandre, Guido van Rossum, Brett Slatkin, Peter Magnusson, Mickey Kataria, Peter McKenzie, sessionabstract: Fireside chat with the App Engine team, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/PYpxM, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/PYpxM, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: fireside-chat-app-engine, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_nN-G4018b0</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dp3nl'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/df9om</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 26</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Full Text Search, sessiontags: Full text search, Datastore, sessionspeakers: Bo Majewski, Ged Ellis, sessionabstract: At last we are adding a full text search service to App Engine. The upcoming service will be built on top of the very infrastructure used by Google. In addition to full text search queries we will also offer numeric, geo, date search capabilities, and much more. This session will cover the basic full text search API, briefly outline more advanced features, and how full text search ties to existing services such as datastore, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/gaIRH, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/gaIRH, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: full-text-search-app-engine, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7B7FyU9wW8Y</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/df9om'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dgo93</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 27</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: Large-scale Data Analysis Using the App Engine Pipeline API, sessiontags: Map Reduce, Pipeline API, sessionspeakers: Brett Slatkin, sessionabstract: The Pipeline API makes it easy to analyze complex data using App Engine. This talk will cover how to build multi-phase Map Reduce workflows; how to merge multiple large data sources with "join" operations; and how to build reusable analysis components. It will also cover the API's concurrency model, how to debug in production, and built-in testing facilities., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/PvMQ7, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/PvMQ7, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: large-scale-data-analysis, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rsfy_TYA2ZY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dgo93'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/di2tg</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 28</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Life in App Engine Production, sessiontags: SRE, Paxos, Monitoring, sessionspeakers: Michael Handler, Alan Green, sessionabstract: App Engine runs your application at scale, so you can focus on features and not sysadminning. But SOMEONE has to run those computers for you! Come meet them, find out what keeps them up at night, and hear hair-raising Tales of the Unexpected. Plus, a demo of new monitoring options for your application, and a dash of HRD advocacy., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/1jWjD, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/1jWjD, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: app-engine-production, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rgQm1KEIIuc</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/di2tg'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/djhdx</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 29</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: More 9s Please: Under The Covers of the High Replication Datastore, sessiontags: High Replication Datastore, Paxos, sessionspeakers: Alfred Fuller, Matt Wilder, sessionabstract: For the first three years of App Engine, the health of the datastore was tied to the health of a single data center.  Users had low latency and strong consistency, but also transient data unavailability and planned read-only periods.  The High Replication Datastore trades small amounts of latency and consistency for significantly higher availability.  In this talk we discuss user-facing and operational issues of the original Master/Slave Datastore, and how the High Replication Datastore addresses these issues., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/7JJtn, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/7JJtn, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: more-9s-please, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xO015C3R6dw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/djhdx'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dw4je</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 30</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Putting Task Queues to Work, sessiontags: Task Queues, Pull queues, sessionspeakers: Nicholas Verne, Vivek Sahasranaman, sessionabstract: Does your app require software that you can't run on App Engine?  By using the brand new pull based queues, you can crunch through all sorts of work like OCR, video encoding, and image manipulation in a VM.  Add work to queues using App Engine's Task Queue API and process the tasks in a VM by pulling from queues using the REST API.  Pull queues open up a lot of new possibilities for your apps so come and hear from the team that built this functionality and bring your questions!, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/YWkUo, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/YWkUo, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: putting-task-queues-to-work, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AM0ZPO7-lcE</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dw4je'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dxj3v</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 31</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: Freebase, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Querying Freebase: Get More From MQL, sessiontags: Freebase, Data, sessionspeakers: Jamie Taylor, sessionabstract: Freebase's query language, MQL, lets you access data about more than 20 million curated entities and the connections between them.  Level up your Freebase query skills with advanced syntax, optimisation tricks, schema introsopection, metaschema, and more., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/0cuT0, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/0cuT0, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: querying-freebase, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1oCeLaCjfO0</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dxj3v'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dyxo8</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 32</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Scaling App Engine Applications, sessiontags: Memcache, Datastore, NDB, sessionspeakers: Justin Haugh, Guido van Rossum, sessionabstract: During this talk, we’ll discuss how to write highly scalable apps on App Engine.  We’ll describe how an app is granted more instances as traffic grows, and the importance of low latency, low memory usage, concurrency, async APIs, load testing, and profiling.  We’ll also help you avoid common pitfalls, like entity contention and hot tablets., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/PWIEy, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/PWIEy, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: scaling-app-engine, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rP-kjrx9CRE</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dyxo8'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e0c8p</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 33</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: Prediction API, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Smart App Design, sessiontags: Prediction API, Android, App Engine, BigQuery, Google Storage for Developers, sessionspeakers: Travis Green, Max Lin, Robert Kaplow, Jóhannes Kristinsson, Ryan McGee, sessionabstract: Learn how to recommend the unexpected, automate the repetitive, and distill the essential using machine learning. This session will show you how you can easily add smarts to your apps with the Prediction API, and how to create apps that rapidly adapt to new data., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/dUVBv, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/dUVBv, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: smart-app-design, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FJDP_0Mrb-w</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e0c8p'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dqi9q</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 34</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: Google Storage for Developers, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Storing Your Application's Data in the Google Cloud, sessiontags: Cloud, Storage, Scalable Data Storage, High Reliability, sessionspeakers: Mike Schwartz, Navneet Joneja, sessionabstract: Google Storage for Developers is a RESTful service for storing and accessing your data on Google's infrastructure. This 101 session shows basic examples of storing data on Google's Cloud, highlights the new features launched since Google I/O 2010, and discusses how to integrate with other Google Developer products, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/j6fLH, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/j6fLH, sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: storing-data-google-cloud, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OsO_UrT8ELI</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dqi9q'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/drwu7</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 35</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: Chrome, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Beyond JavaScript: Programming the Web with Native Client, sessiontags: Chrome, HTML5, JavaScript, Native Client, sessionspeakers: David Springer, sessionabstract: Learn how to supercharge your web apps with native C/C++ code that runs directly in the browser, without the hassle of a plug-in.  Join us as we build a simple game that has a simulation engine built in C/C++ and a front-end built in Javascript.  You'll learn how to serve the native code and how to connect the C/C++ code to Javascript., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/sR83G, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/sR83G, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: beyond-javascript-native-client, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WgbK0ztUkDM</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/drwu7'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dtbek</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 36</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: Chrome Web Store, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Chrome Web Store Publisher Panel, sessiontags: Chrome, Chrome Web Store, sessionspeakers: Seth Ladd, Jason Horman, Andre Behrens, YuChiang Cheng, sessionabstract: Hear first-hand experience and lessons learned from Chrome Web Store developers and publishers.  We'll cover business and technology experiences, and re-tell stories: both good and bad.  Learn from New York Times, Springpad, and World Golf Tour in this interactive and informal panel discussion., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/HTeFw, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/HTeFw, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: chrome-web-store-lessons, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HL-NtsUsWuw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dtbek'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dupz1</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 37</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: Cloud, HTML5, Accessibility, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Creating Accessible Interactive Web Apps using HTML5, sessiontags: Chrome, access, HTML5, sessionspeakers: Dominic Mazzoni, Rachel Shearer, sessionabstract: Providing a basic HTML site used to be the best way to make sure your content was accessible to all users. But times have changed, and now you can use HTML5 techniques to provide an experience that's just as rich and interactive for people who use assistive technology. The emphasis of this talk will be on techniques that work today in the latest browser versions. Techniques covered will include proper use of ARIA along with focus management and keyboard navigation., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/xoz6I, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/xoz6I, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: accessible-apps-html5, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lMrkCoqgoxw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/dupz1'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e7d2q</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 38</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: Chrome, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Fireside Chat with the Chrome Team, sessiontags: chrome, sessionspeakers: Ian Ellison-Taylor, Alex Russell, Pavel Feldman, Jeff Chang, Erik Kay, sessionabstract: Fireside chat with the Chrome team., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/qy40k, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/qy40k, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: fireside-chat-chrome, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQZu6azNlA0</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e7d2q'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e8rn7</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 39</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: HTML5, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: HTML5 &amp; What's Next, sessiontags: HTML5, JS, CSS, DOM, Chrome, WebKit, UX, sessionspeakers: Alex Russell, Ian Fette, Alex Komoroske, sessionabstract: Mobile and desktop are converging on HTML5 as a strong, portable base for delivering rich experiences. Come learn about the future of HTML5, CSS, DOM, and JavaScript that will help you build better, richer apps even faster., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/UtSYG, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/UtSYG, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: html5-whats-next, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qzA60hHca9s</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e8rn7'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ea67k</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 40</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: HTML5, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: HTML5 Showcase for Web Developers: The Wow and the How, sessiontags: Chrome, HTML, JS, CSS, sessionspeakers: Eric Bidelman, Arne Roomann-Kurrik, sessionabstract: We'll share the strengths and extents of HTML5, showing magnificent demos of bleeding-edge features in Google Chrome. Digging into high-fidelity graphics, performance, and system integration, we’ll break each demo down on the big screen to show how it was constructed.  Then we’ll show you how to use Chrome to its full potential in your own projects., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/c6kgn, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/c6kgn, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: html5-showcase-wow-how, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WlwY6_W4VG8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ea67k'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ebks1</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 41</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: Chrome Frame, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: HTML5 Today with Google Chrome Frame, sessiontags: web developer, HTML5, sessionspeakers: Alex Russell, Amit Joshi, sessionabstract: Chrome Frame empowers developers of HTML5 web applications to fully support Internet Explorer without having to maintain separate versions of their sites.  Find out how easy it is to integrate GCF with your site and take advantage of HTML5., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ezlN8, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ezlN8, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: html5-today-chrome-frame, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3YkEUpJQP3o</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ebks1'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e35dj</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 42</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: HTML5, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Mobile Web Development: From Zero to Hero, sessiontags: HTML5, JS, UX, Chrome, Mobile Webkit, sessionspeakers: Michael Mahemoff, Paul Kinlan, sessionabstract: Explosive growth in the mobile web is set to continue.  Don't leave yourself behind.  Writing a new app in every native environment is not always possible, and HTML5 is a way to reuse the bulk of your code across all major platforms. We will show you step-by-step how to build an amazing web app that works on many devices., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/GxUNM, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/GxUNM, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: mobile-web-development, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vV85dNeGRhY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e35dj'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e4jxw</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 43</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: Chrome, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Super Browser 2 Turbo HD Remix: Introduction to HTML5 Game Development, sessiontags: HTML5, sessionspeakers: Seth Ladd, sessionabstract: HTML5 provides the foundation for rich and interactive experiences. Which is great, but we really want to build and play games!  Learn the basics of building an HTML5 game and explore the related technologies.  We'll write a simple game and give you the tools and techniques to create your own worlds and fun., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/bb8Is, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/bb8Is, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: super-browser-2-turbo-hd, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yEocRtn_j9s</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e4jxw'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e5yid</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 44</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: Google Fonts, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Web Fonts are changing the Web. Learn why., sessiontags: fonts, sessionspeakers: David Wurtz, David Kuettel, Raph Levien, Darren Glenister, sessionabstract: Web fonts have reached a tipping point. In the next few years, the majority of new websites will be built with web fonts. Learn about the benefits of using web fonts in your applications and webpages, some exciting new web font tools that integrate into your existing workflows as well as the technology behind Google Fonts., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/sGOYg, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/sGOYg, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: web-fonts-changing-web, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QTX1lU97z08</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/e5yid'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eilm2</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 45</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 3, sessionproduct: HTML5, sessiontrack: Chrome, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: WebGL Techniques and Performance, sessiontags: HTML5, JS, WebGL, GL, Graphics, Canvas, sessionspeakers: Gregg Tavares, sessionabstract: WebGL is in most major browsers. Learn the techniques needed to get the maximum performance from WebGL. We'll go over how to draw the most models, particles and grass systems, creative use of uv offsets and other effects., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/hX9Xe, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/hX9Xe, sessionhashtag: Chrome, sessionslug: webgl-techniques-performance, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rfQ8rKGTVlg</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eilm2'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ek06j</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 46</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: Checkout, sessiontrack: Commerce, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Google Checkout: A Foundation For Payments, sessiontags: commerce, sessionspeakers: Peng Ying, Mihai Ionescu, Satyajeet Salgar, Rett Clevenger, Marco Rodriguez, sessionabstract: Google Checkout has matured and is now the platform for Google’s Commerce initiatives.  This session will provide you a foundation of knowledge for leveraging Google Commerce.  We’ll define what Checkout is and how it’s different from other payment processors and review the current API functionality.  We’ll then dive into current developments, simple yet powerful tools we’ve created to leverage Checkout., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/VFwu5, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/VFwu5, sessionhashtag: Commerce, sessionslug: google-checkout-foundation-payments, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ts7Lkykn0E</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ek06j'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eleqw</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 47</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 7, sessiontrack: Commerce, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Google One Pass: A simple, flexible, Web API for paywalls, sessionspeakers: Omi Chandiramani, Chase Hensel, sessionabstract: Learn how to monetize and control access to your digital content across browsers and devices in a pay once, access anywhere model from Google One Pass, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/GpSgG, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/GpSgG, sessionhashtag: Commerce, sessionslug: google-one-pass, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=reRIC1lAwfo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eleqw'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/emtbd</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 48</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: eBooks, sessiontrack: Commerce, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Integrating to eBooks: APIs to Sell and Read eBooks for Affiliates, Retailers and Device Makers, sessiontags: eBooks, books, commerce, Google APIs, EDItX, GData, ACS4, OAuth, ONIX, XML, sessionspeakers: Kevin Landry, Pratip Banerji, sessionabstract: Learn how independent booksellers, book-centric web sites, and e-reader device makers are using Google eBooks APIs to extend their reach in the digital book marketplace.  See how Google Affiliate Network, GData API for books, EDItX XML standards, OAuth, and Adobe DRM enable a range of eBook integrations., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/Gkvhz, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/Gkvhz, sessionhashtag: Commerce, sessionslug: integrating-ebooks, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6F8wyr7pqw4</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/emtbd'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eczce</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 49</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: Payments/Chrome, sessiontrack: Commerce, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Introducing In-App Payments for the Web, sessiontags: API, Payments, Flash, sessionspeakers: Amit Fulay, Mikhail Seregine, Luke Bayes, Jacob McMahon, sessionabstract: We will introduce in-app Payments API for monetizing games, content and digital goods. We will show demos and example integrations, as well as walk through how the API works and how to integrate it into both HTML and Flash apps., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/SKJIv, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/SKJIv, sessionhashtag: Commerce, sessionslug: introducing-in-app-payments-web, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bAcyP06KqPs</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eczce'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eedwv</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 50</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: Google Shopping , sessiontrack: Commerce, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Introduction to Google Shopping APIs, sessionspeakers: Nitin Mangtani, Ali Afshar, sessionabstract: We recently launched the newest addition to the Google shopping family -- a simple yet powerful programmatic interface that enables developers to upload their product data and query product data from Google. The new Shopping Application Programming Interfaces (APIs) have two main components: Content and Search. In this session, we will walk you through an initial introduction into these APIs., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/0mbhq, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/0mbhq, sessionhashtag: Commerce, sessionslug: google-shopping-apis, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8mahQ5jIBUs</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eedwv'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/efsh8</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 51</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct:  GWT, Cloud, Chrome, Eclipse Tooling , sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Bring the Cloud to Your IDE with the Google Plugin for Eclipse, sessiontags: App Engine, Cloud, Goole APIs, Eclipse, Java, GPE, HTML, CSS, JavaScript , sessionspeakers: Rajeev Dayal, sessionabstract: With the cloud you can now run services that previously couldn't run on or be accessible from a typical desktop machine. The ability to harness cloud services and infrastructure within apps adds huge value for your users. One of the easiest ways to add the power of the cloud to your apps is with the cloud-connected Google Plugin for Eclipse., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/hw0ak, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/hw0ak, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: cloud-ide-google-plugin, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V0vOVWA9yJs</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/efsh8'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eh71p</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 52</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 8, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Building Game Development Tools with App Engine, GWT, and WebGL, sessiontags: Games, App Engine, sessionspeakers: Lilli Thompson, sessionabstract: Sure App Engine is a great platform for building online games, but have you considered that it’s also a great platform for building game development tools? As social gaming platforms become more capable, developers are faced with increasingly complex art and design data. This session will discuss using App Engine, GWT, and WebGL to build tools that support game development and asset management., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/w2uLN, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/w2uLN, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: building-game-development-tools, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NNmoEOpGJdk</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eh71p'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/etu5e</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 53</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: Chrome Dev Tools, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Chrome Dev Tools Reloaded , sessiontags: Chrome, Dev Tools, HTML5, JS, sessionspeakers: Paul Irish, Pavel Feldman, sessionabstract: You're an experienced web developer but new to Chrome Dev Tools' nuances? Get up to speed on all the newest features of a web app developer's best friend. Update CSS styles on the fly, get a diff or save changes to disk. Set breakpoints on everything imaginable and dig into the networking stack to uncover performance gains., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/Qfji5, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/Qfji5, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: chrome-dev-tools-reloaded, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N8SS-rUEZPg</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/etu5e'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ev8pv</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 54</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: GWT, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Fireside Chat with the GWT and Cloud Tooling Team, sessiontags: Fireside chat, GWT, sessionspeakers: Ray Ryan, John Tamplin, Jaime Wren, Jason Rosenberg, Phil Quintslund, Stephanie Brubaker, Unnur Gretarsdottir, Bruce Johnson, sessionabstract: Here’s your chance to find out what the GWT team has been up to since 2.2. Several core engineers will discuss the new features and frameworks in GWT and answer your questions.	, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/s7Ilz, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/s7Ilz, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: fireside-chat-gwt-cloud-tooling, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n3hBzIOUSms</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ev8pv'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ewna8</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 55</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: GWT, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: GWT + HTML5: A web developers dream!, sessiontags: Ajax, HTML, GWT, sessionspeakers: John Labanca, sessionabstract: How can you take advantage of new HTML5 features in your GWT applications? In this session, we answer that question in the form of demos -- lots and lots of demos. We'll cover examples of how to use Canvas (for visualizations), drag and drop, CSS3 features, and more within your GWT applications., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/oKqEG, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/oKqEG, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: gwt-html5-web-dream, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KEkR1ox_K10</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ewna8'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ey1up</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 56</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: GWT, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: GWT + UI Designer: Enterprise Web UIs Made Easy!, sessiontags: GWT, sessionspeakers: Eric Clayberg, sessionabstract: We'll look at how enterprise developers can use Google Web Toolkit and the new UI Designer in Google Plugin for Eclipse to quickly build web user interfaces that are not only fast, lightweight and cross-browser compatible but reusable and easy to maintain as well., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/S3U2K, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/S3U2K, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: gwt-ui-designer-enterprise, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kV5H3rGfqOE</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ey1up'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eo7vq</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 57</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: GWT, Chrome, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: High-performance GWT: best practices for writing smaller, faster apps, sessiontags: perf, GWT, Ajax, sessionspeakers: David Chandler, sessionabstract: The GWT compiler isn't just a Java to JavaScript transliterator. In this session, we'll show you compiler optimizations to shrink your app and make it compile and run faster. Learn common performance pitfalls, how to use lightweight cell widgets, how to use code splitting with Activities and Places, and compiler options to reduce your app's size and compile time., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/agZ31, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/agZ31, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: high-performance-gwt, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0F5zc1UAt2Y</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/eo7vq'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/epmg7</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 58</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: GWT, Ecllipse Tooling, Apps Marketplace, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Highly Productive GWT: Rapid Development with App Engine, Objectify, RequestFactory, and gwt-platform, sessiontags: GWT, Eclipse, App Engine, sessionspeakers: David Chandler, Philippe Beaudoin, Jeff Schnitzer, sessionabstract: In this session you’ll learn how to use popular Google and third party tools to build a robust and maintainable GWT+GAE app. We'll use Google Plugin for Eclipse, Objectify-App Engine with GWT's RequestFactory for persistence, and gwt-platform (GWT MVP framework) for the UI., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/j8phu, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/j8phu, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: highly-productive-gwt, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=imiquTOLl64</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/epmg7'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/er10k</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 59</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: Closure Tools, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: JavaScript Programming in the Large with Closure Tools, sessiontags: JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Michael Bolin, sessionabstract: Most developers who have tinkered with JavaScript could not imagine writing 1,000 lines of code in such a language, let alone 100,000. Yet that is exactly what Google engineers have done using a suite of JavaScript tools named “Closure” to produce many of the most popular and sophisticated applications on the Web, such as Gmail and Google Maps., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/tKIhB, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/tKIhB, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: javascript-programming-closure, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M3uWx-fhjUc</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/er10k'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/esfl1</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 60</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 5, sessionproduct: GWT, Android, Chrome, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Kick-ass Game Programming with Google Web Toolkit, sessiontags: Games, GWT, HTML5, WebGL, Android, sessionspeakers: Ray Cromwell, Philip Rogers, sessionabstract: GWT does more than make awesome Enterprise Apps, it's a great tool for games too. Learn to write 2D and 3D games using HTML5 and GWT, leverage and port existing game libraries and physics engines, share game code between GWT and Android, publish to the Chrome Web Store, and of course, see demos of really neat GWT games in action., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/GeRsG, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/GeRsG, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: kick-ass-game-programming-gwt, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_sbusEUz5w</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/esfl1'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a59y2</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 61</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: Page Speed for Mobile, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Use Page Speed to Optimize Your Web Site For Mobile, sessiontags: HTML5, Mobile, Android, Make the web faster, web development, sessionspeakers: Bryan McQuade, Libo Song, Claudia Dent, sessionabstract: Use Page Speed to evaluate the performance of your web pages and to get suggestions on how to improve them with the newest web development optimizations. Attendees will learn how to make their sites load faster in the browser, with an emphasis on how to optimize mobile web site performance. Compuware will showcase mobile Page Speed integration in their developer tools., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/POoh0, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/POoh0, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: page-speed-optimize-mobile, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_MuVoabSLeY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a59y2'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a6oij</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 62</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: GWT, Android, Chrome, Eclipse Tooling , sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Using GWT and Eclipse to Build Great Mobile Web Apps, sessiontags: Android, App Engine, Cloud, Eclipse, Java, ADT, GPE, HTML, CSS, JavaScript , sessionspeakers: Chris Ramsdale, sessionabstract: Mobile web application development is HOT. But many developers are already familiar with web technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and GWT for building modern web applications. In this talk we will discuss how you can use these skills, and code, to build great web apps for mobile devices., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/BRgTA, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/BRgTA, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: gwt-eclipse-great-mobile, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N1aCo5LvMf8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a6oij'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a832w</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 63</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: Go, sessiontrack: Developer Tools, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Writing Web Apps in Go, sessiontags: Go, Web, sessionspeakers: Andrew Gerrand, Rob Pike, sessionabstract: Web back-end languages tend to be a matter of "Speed, reliability, or simplicity: pick one." Not any more. The Go Programming Language is a rock-solid, productive, and high-performance platform for building web applications (and other types of software). Join the Go team for an entertaining, in-depth look at the development and deployment of a Go web application., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/HFvWZ, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/HFvWZ, sessionhashtag: DevTools, sessionslug: web-apps-in-go, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-i0hat7pdpk</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a832w'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/i6mvg</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 64</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 8, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Connecting People and Places, sessiontags: Maps, Location, Local, Places, Mobile, sessionspeakers: Marissa Mayer, Thor Mitchell, sessionabstract: Hear how Google Maps and Google Places connect millions of people to the places around them, and how your applications can do so too., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/9Yplh, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/9Yplh, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: connecting-people-and-places, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7q6Z-3aeg8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/i6mvg'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a9hnd</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 65</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: Maps API v3, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: Designing Maps Applications for Usability on Mobile and Desktop, sessiontags: Maps, Usability, UX, UI, Mobile, sessionspeakers: Luke Mahé, Jez Fletcher, Justin O'Beirne, sessionabstract: Maps API applications are accessed on desktop and mobile devices of many shapes and sizes. Each application has unique goals for conveying information effectively and for facilitating user interactions. Learn how to improve user experience by optimizing the presentation of your map and data and by thoughtful user interface design., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/BJf2Y, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/BJf2Y, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: designing-maps-applications-usability, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ckngV52m2Yg</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a9hnd'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/9znoe</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 66</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 7, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Fireside Chat with the Geo team, sessionspeakers: Thor Mitchell, Peter Birch, Rebecca Shapley, Dan Chu, Susannah Raub, Jayant Madhavan, sessionabstract: Fireside Chat with the Geo team., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/0NJAO, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/0NJAO, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: fireside-chat-geo, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qo8g4x2OkPs</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/9znoe'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a128v</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 67</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: Fusion Tables, Maps API v3, Earth Builder, Earth Engine, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: GIS with Google Earth and Google Maps, sessiontags: GIS, Maps, Earth, sessionspeakers: Josh Livni, Mano Marks, sessionabstract: Building a robust interactive map with a lot of data involves more than just adding a few placemarks.  We'll talk about integrating with existing GIS software, importing data from shapefiles and other formats, map projections, and techniques for managing, analyzing, and rendering large datasets., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/01I2W, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/01I2W, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: gis-google-earth-maps, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O1FpDKckCGk</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a128v'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a2gt8</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 68</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: KML, Earth, Earth API, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: High Performance KML for Maps and Earth, sessiontags: KML, Earth, Maps, GIS, sessionspeakers: Sean Askay, Mano Marks, sessionabstract: KML is the most used geographic display language in the world. As the volume of data that needs to be displayed on a Map or in Google Earth increases, an awareness perfomance becomes increasingly important. We will be discussing techniques for reducing bandwidth usage, applying incremental changes, styling, and other ways to supercharge your KML., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/AKGHb, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/AKGHb, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: high-performance-kml, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nIoWHlEEeNI</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a2gt8'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a3vdp</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 69</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: Places API, Maps API, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Location Based App development using Google APIs, sessiontags: Mobile, Location, Social, Places, sessionspeakers: Marcelo Camelo, Thor Mitchell, Yoni Samlan, sessionabstract: Check-in to this session and discover how Google APIs such as the Places API, Buzz API, and Latitude API can provide you with the services you need to build the next great location based app., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/FScsb, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/FScsb, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: location-based-app-development, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nuDgC7RspsQ</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/a3vdp'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/agihe</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 70</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: Fusion Tables, Maps API v3, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Managing and visualizing your geospatial data with Fusion Tables, sessiontags: Fusion Tables, Maps, Cloud, sessionspeakers: Kathryn Hurley, James McGill, Simon Rogers, sessionabstract: Geospatial data has special requirements that aren't met by traditional database or cloud data storage. Google Fusion Tables offers a unique, easy way to upload, store, share, visualize, and manage your geospatial data. We'll walk you through how you can use Fusion Tables in your spatial data applications, covering the API, permissions, sharing, data collection, and advanced techniques., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/YZiWK, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/YZiWK, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: geospatial-data-fusion-tables, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z2o0mtnF1Bg</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/agihe'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ahx1v</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 71</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: Maps API v3, Street View API, Fusion Tables, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Map your business, inside and out, sessiontags: Maps, Street View, Fusion Tables, sessionspeakers: Brendan Kenny, Chris Broadfoot, sessionabstract: Your map doesn't have to end at the front door of the building! In this session we will discuss approaches to mapping all of your business locations, and not just on the outside. We'll show how to build a sensational storefinder, and then add floorplans, indoor Street View, and resource search., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/UsTkN, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/UsTkN, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: map-your-business-inside-out, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ATfdi-oYWzw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ahx1v'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ajbm8</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 72</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: Maps API, Earth API, Fusion Tables API, KML, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Secrets and surprises of the Google Geo APIs, sessiontags: Maps, Earth, KML. Fusion Tables, sessionspeakers: Ossama Alami, Aaron Jacobs, sessionabstract: We've been busy this year! Come learn about some new, some hidden, and some surprising features of the Maps API, Earth API, Fusion Tables and other APIs you may not even realise exist., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/Umylp, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/Umylp, sessionhashtag: Geo, sessionslug: secrets-surprises-geo-apis, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=luv84lxCRwo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ajbm8'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/akq6p</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 73</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: Maps API v3, Fusion Tables, sessiontrack: Geo, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: Speedy Maps, sessiontags: Maps, Mobile, Performance, sessionspeakers: Susannah Raub, Dave Day, sessionabstract: Fast maps make users happy. Come and discover a multitude of ways you can optimize your map performance from loading the map to displaying thousands of overlays. Learn how to identify the bottlenecks in your application so you can give your maps the tuneups they need., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/dpqTV, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/dpqTV, sessionhashtag: geo, sessionslug: speedy-maps, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7pCh62wr6m0</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/akq6p'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/aaw7q</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 74</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: Google+1, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: An introduction to the +1 button, sessionspeakers: Timothy Jordan, sessionabstract: The +1 buttons let people who love your content recommend it on Google search and on your site.  In this session you’ll learn all about the +1 button and how it can help your site stand out.  We’ll cover the value and impact of the +1 action, how to embed it on your site, custom configurations, and how to optimize with analytics., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/W7aVd, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/W7aVd, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: introduction-plusone-button, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fl3c79n_wRg</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/aaw7q'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/acas7</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 75</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: Blogger, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Building a Business Web Presence using Blogger APIs, sessiontags: Blogger, Google APIs, sessionspeakers: Brett Morgan, Pat Coleman, sessionabstract: Want to sell a website hosting solution to your clients that won’t keep you awake at night with the fear it might get crushed by becoming virally popular? Blogger’s new Admin APIs enable you to have a customer friendly interface that serves their needs, and yours. Come along and learn how to implement your next customer site atop Blogger., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/p2odI, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/p2odI, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: web-presence-blogger-apis, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BazoWR1kYbM</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/acas7'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/adpck</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 76</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 4, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Building Custom Client Libraries for Google APIs, sessiontags: Google APIs, Java, Python, Client Library, Discovery, sessionspeakers: Monsur Hossain, Joe Gregorio, Anton Lopyrev, sessionabstract: Although Google offers client libraries to access our APIs for a variety of languages, there are some languages out there that don’t yet have client library. In this session, we will demonstrate how you can easily build a client library for your favorite language using the new API Discovery service. Join us and learn how you can make it even easier to use Google APIs in your preferred programming environment., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/CyYj7, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/CyYj7, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: building-custom-client-libraries, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lQbT1NrxpUo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/adpck'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/af3x1</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 77</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: ClientLogin. OAuth2, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: ClientLogin #FAIL, sessiontags: ClientLogin, OAuth2, , sessionspeakers: Dirk Balfanz, sessionabstract: If you know what ClientLogin is, and have an app that uses it, you need to attend this session to learn why ClientLogin is not a good choice for your users.  This session will cover the problems with ClientLogin that Google as described in posts such as http://apiblog.youtube.com/2011/03/clientlogin-fail.html.  We will also cover best-practices for moving from ClientLogin to OAuth2., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/HHQsq, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/HHQsq, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: clientlogin-fail, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fud6NKljgPU</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/af3x1'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/arr0q</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 78</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 9, sessionproduct: Mobile monetization, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Implementing Money Making SDKs, sessiontags: mobile, monetization, ads, AdMob, Analytics, Android, mediation, sessionspeakers: Mike Ying, Dean Browne, Paul Hounshell, sessionabstract: Watch our experts integrate the Google AdMob Ads SDK across Android, iOS and Windows Phone 7. Learn integration tips and tricks so you can start making money from your app today, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/zntSX, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/zntSX, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: implementing-money-making-sdks, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cc0JqolMBww</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/arr0q'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/at5l7</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 79</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 1, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Life of a Google API Developer, sessiontags: Google APIs, Client Libraries, sessionspeakers: David Gibson, Tony Aiuto, Mark Stahl, sessionabstract: Over the past year, Google has launched several APIs, including Buzz, URL Shortener and Latitude, among others, that are built on the new API infrastructure presented at last year's I/O.  We've also completely rebuilt our client libraries and have launched several new tools to help you learn about our APIs, bootstrap your development, and register your app with Google.  In this session, we dive into the life of a Google API developer, covering the steps needed to develop an application on top of these new Google APIs and best practices for using them., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/aY5OD, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/aY5OD, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: life-of-google-api-developer, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=62RxWSzQ-0o</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/at5l7'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/auk5k</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 80</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: Google+1, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Scalable Structured Markup, sessionspeakers: Timothy Jordan, sessionabstract: Structured markup tells Google and the world what your page is really about.  It can help you create a richer experience around content on your site or app while driving greater traffic and engagement.  It can also help connect your app with information found on the open web.  We’ll cover the different types of markup, how Google uses markup, using Webmaster Tools to validate, and automating updates., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/dLsyG, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/dLsyG, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: scalable-structured-markup, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pt6_cxvCWEw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/auk5k'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/avyq1</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 81</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: YouTube, Accessibility, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: The YouTube Caption API, Speech Recognition, and WebVTT captions for HTML5, sessiontags: YouTube, Accessibility, translation, speech recognition, App Engine, captions, Google APIs, webVTT, HTML5, sessionspeakers: Naomi Black, Cynthia Boedihardjo, Jeffrey Posnick, sessionabstract: Captions make video accessible and more importantly: discoverable to search. Learn how we're live captioning Google I/O with a new open source gadget, discover caption features in the YouTube Data API based on speech recognition, and find out more about WebVTT, a new format to help broadcast TV subtitling make the leap to HTML5 and the Web. , sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/2RmW8, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/2RmW8, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: youtube-caption-api, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tua3DdacgOo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/avyq1'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/am4r2</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 82</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 1, sessionproduct: Chart Tools, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201/301, sessiontitle: Using Google Chart Tools to Create Interactive Dashboards, sessiontags: Charts, Visualization, Data, Dashboards, Chart Editor, Animations, sessionspeakers: Michael Fink, Riccardo Govoni, Amit Weinstein, sessionabstract: Demonstrate how our new HTML5 visualization gallery and data exploration components can be composed in a matter of minutes to generate sexy interactive dashboards., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/DPzsO, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/DPzsO, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: using-google-chart-tools, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NZtgT4jgnE8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/am4r2'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/anjbj</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 83</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: YouTube, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Your Game + YouTube = Instant Community, sessiontags: YouTube, sessionspeakers: Jarek Wilkiewicz, Doug Muir, sessionabstract: Activision’s YouTube API integration in Call of Duty: Black Ops led to over a million user-generated uploads in less than 4 months. We’ll cover the details of that integration and explore best practices for building a YouTube community around your own video game!, sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/tbHG8, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/tbHG8, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: your-game-youtube-instant, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9cBBHyZWADo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/anjbj'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/aoxvw</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 84</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 4, sessionproduct: YouTube, sessiontrack: Google APIs, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: YouTube's iframe Player: The Future of Embedding, sessiontags: YouTube, HTML5, JavaScript, Flash, video, sessionspeakers: Jeffrey Posnick, Jarek Wilkiewicz, Greg Schechter, sessionabstract: YouTube players allow for video playback in web applications. The latest YouTube's embedded iframe player supports both Flash and HTML5 video and exposes a rich API which lets you control the YouTube playback experience. We'll give you the details on how the API was developed, and show you how it can power the videos on your own website., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/TxoeV, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/TxoeV, sessionhashtag: GoogleAPIs, sessionslug: youtubes-iframe-player, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bHQqvYy5KYo</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/aoxvw'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/aqcgd</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 85</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Google Apps, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Apps Marketplace: Best Practices and Integrations, sessionspeakers: Steven Bazyl, sessionabstract: Just over 1 year ago the Google Apps Marketplace launched with 50 cloud apps integrated with Google Apps.  Today, there are over 300 apps and growing.  In this session we'll go over highlight some the best practices found in applications and explore how apps take advantage of APIs like contacts, docs, calendar, and gadgets to provide additional value for their users., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/hyl6Y, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/hyl6Y, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: apps-marketplace-best-practices, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KKQS8EDG1P4</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/aqcgd'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b4e4j</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 86</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: App Engine, Cloud Storage, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Compliance and Security in the Cloud: Essential Administrative APIs for Google Apps Businesses, sessiontags: Google Apps, SAML, Provisioning, Auditing, sessionspeakers: Michael Manoochehri, sessionabstract: Learn what you need to know to succeed as a Google Apps VAR or customer in the areas of identity management, data migration, reporting, and auditing., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/cvWEb, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/cvWEb, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: compliance-security-cloud, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T51xcOpz6Js</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b4e4j'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b5sow</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 87</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Google Apps Script, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Developing Apps, Add Ins and More with Google Apps Script, sessionspeakers: Evin Levey, Mike Harm, Drew Csillag, James Ferreira, sessionabstract: This intermediate talk focuses on some less well known uses of Apps Script - building Add Ins for Google Apps, standalone applications and more!  We'll focus on rapid application development features, and demonstrate deployment to several targets., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/w07ka, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/w07ka, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: developing-apps-add-ins-more, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DOih39gu0xw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b5sow'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b779d</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 88</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Google Apps, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Developing innovative custom business solutions with Google Apps, sessiontags: Google Apps, ISV, Apps Marketplace, sessionspeakers: Jeff Ragusa, sessionabstract: Increasingly VARs and integrators are bringing cloud apps from multiple vendors to their customers to create comprehensive and custom solutions.  This session will show some of the innovative solutions developed by Google Apps resellers to tie multiple business systems together with Google Apps for increased organizational productivity.  We'll learn how one integrator migrated a business' systems, data, and processes to the web using a slick combination of Google Sites and App Engine on the back end, Gadgets and Google Web Toolkit on the front end, and business process workflow powered by Google Apps Script., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/lF9he, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/lF9he, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: developing-innovative-business-solutions, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JXe0awIsR9I</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b779d'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/axdae</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 89</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Google Apps Script, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Enterprise Workflow with Apps Script, sessiontags: Apps Script, Google Apps, sessionspeakers: Evin Levey, Eric Zhang, Corey Goldfeder, sessionabstract: Developing comprehensive and user friendly workflow can be a time consuming and thankless task.  We showcase several new features of Apps Script and demonstrate how they make workflow easier., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/zQqFD, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/zQqFD, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: enterprise-workflow-apps-script, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=96URE_-aj-8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/axdae'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ayruv</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 90</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Apps Marketplace, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Launch and Grow Your Business App on the Google Apps Marketplace, sessiontags: Google Apps, ISVs, VARs, Apps Marketplace, sessionspeakers: Scott McMullan, Matt Trifiro, Cameron Henneke, Jim McNelis, sessionabstract: The Google Apps Marketplace is an online store to discover and purchase web applications which are integrated with Google Apps.  This introductory session will provide an overview of the Google Apps Marketplace.  You'll learn product integration and marketing best practices directly from Marketplace vendors., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/K8gXh, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/K8gXh, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: launch-grow-apps-marketplace, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HnW_Y9nRiEY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ayruv'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b06f8</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 91</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Google Docs APIs, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Using The Google Docs APIs To Store All Your Information In The Cloud, sessiontags: Google Documents List API, Data, sessionspeakers: Vic Fryzel, sessionabstract: This session will discuss in detail how to store files in the cloud, integrating with existing applications. We will work through code examples and a working application., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/sg4t1, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/sg4t1, sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: google-docs-apis-store-cloud, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sp8fotnTwj8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b06f8'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b1kzp</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 92</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 7, sessionproduct: General Engineering, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Accessibility: Building Products that Everyone Can Use, sessiontags: access, accessibility, disability, eyesfree, ARIA, Chrome, Chrome Extensions, Android, captions, YouTube, HTML5, ADA, 508, sessionspeakers: Brad Green, Erin Rosenthal, Steve Jacobs, Jaehong Chon, sessionabstract: Whether your users are blind, deaf, dyslexic, or simply driving a car, making apps accessible provides a richer experience for all. Using examples and demos, we'll give you an overview of what it means to make web and Android applications accessible. You'll see that accessible doesn't mean boring. , sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/bqY7g, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/bqY7g, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: accessibility-building-products, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAzY2MQxJDQ</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b1kzp'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/be856</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 93</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 5, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Building Web Apps for Google TV, sessiontags: TV, JavaScript, HTML5, Flash, Chrome, sessionspeakers: Chris Wilson, Daniels Lee, sessionabstract: Learn about the Google TV platform and the opportunity to build web apps for the platform using HTML5 or Flash.  Session includes an overview of the platform, best practices, demos, and a discussion about the opportunities for developers to build killer apps for Google TV., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/zqoKD, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/zqoKD, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: building-web-apps-google-tv, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n8hjjSzgRyw</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/be856'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bfmpn</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 94</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, sessionroom: 5, sessionproduct: Cloud Robotics, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Cloud Robotics, sessiontags: Android, Java, Python, Robots, Cloud, Education, sessionspeakers: Ryan Hickman, Damon Kohler, Jonathan Pale, Ken Conley, Brian Gerkey, sessionabstract: Learn how developers can accelerate the pace of robotics research and development and make high functioning robots affordable and universally accessible., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/PLTk7, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/PLTk7, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: cloud-robotics, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FxXBUp-4800</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bfmpn'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bh1a0</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 95</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, sessionroom: 5, sessionproduct: TableCast / Fusion Tables, App Engine - Resource Finder / Person Finder / DataWiki,
Public Alerts (DotOrg), sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Crisis Response 2.0 - Empowering Developers in Times of Crisis, sessiontags: app-engine, fusion tables, disaster, crisis, dotorg, python, java, XML, sessionspeakers: Prem Ramaswami, Steve Hakusa, sessionabstract: In the last decade, pervasive cellular data and Internet access have enabled new approaches to saving lives and reducing misery in times of crisis. Several organizations are developing systems to help disaster responders and people affected by a disaster. We hope to introduce some of the new standards and products Google is developing to help the crisis response ecosystem., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/Xu5xh, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/Xu5xh, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: crisis-response-two, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5olMWz0-Pxc</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bh1a0'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bifuh</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 96</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 5:00pm-6:25pm, sessionroom: Lunch Room, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Google Ventures Meetup, sessionabstract: Please join &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/ventures"&gt;Google Ventures&lt;/a&gt; in an experiment in “controlled chaos!” This session will bring Google I|O attendees together with members of Google Ventures' core team (investors and experienced startup veterans), and select portfolio companies (ranging from small, new teams...to later-stage, successful companies).  The room will be arranged enabling attendees to speak to panels of "experts" in bite-sized, three-minute 1:1 conversations. Otherwise known as VC speed dating! Our goal is to connect both practicing, and soon-to-be entrepreneurs, with experts who can impart advice, lessons learned, and quick tips., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/GgqxF, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/GgqxF, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: google-ventures-meetup</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bifuh'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b8lvi</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 97</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 5, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: How to Get Your Startup Idea Funded by Venture Capitalists, sessiontags: VC, Funding, sessionspeakers: Don Dodge, Joe Kraus, Paul Buchheit, Seth Priebatsch, sessionabstract: Have an idea and want to start a company? Learn how to attract investors, and what they want to see before writing a check. Hear from entrepreneurs who have raised money and VCs who have funded them., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/tiB2s, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/tiB2s, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: get-startup-idea-funded, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=15iWltPLuPY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/b8lvi'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ba0fz</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 98</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, sessionroom: 5, sessionproduct: OpenID, OAuth, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Identity and Data Access: OpenID and OAuth, sessiontags: OpenID, OAuth, Identity, Data Access, sessionspeakers: Ryan Boyd, sessionabstract: Use OpenID and OAuth to stop requiring your users to type usernames and passwords. In this session, we’ll demonstrate how to improve user experience and lower barriers to entry for your application by using OpenID.  We’ll show how to securely access powerful user data securely using OAuth.  We'll also talk about which flavors of these technologies should be used for common use cases., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/TmcV9, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/TmcV9, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: identity-data-access-openid-oauth, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SLsfzTNIykY</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/ba0fz'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bbf0c</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 99</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 5:00pm-6:00pm, sessionroom: 3, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Ignite, sessionspeakers: Brady Forrest, Kyle Machulis, Matt Cutts, Pamela Fox, Jamie Wilkinson, Patrick Davison, Monica Rogati, Annalee Newitz, Joseph Pred, Kevin Marks, John Adams, sessionabstract: Ignite is back to top off your brain after a packed day. This year we will learn about the Brain API, the similarities of Disneyland and Burning Man, and a dissection of the Tiger Mom myth. As always the speakers will have just 20 slides that auto-advance every 15 seconds for a total of five minutes on stage., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/hkrAf, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/hkrAf, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: ignite, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52Ml_zax4A0</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bbf0c'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bctkt</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 100</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: Java, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Java Puzzlers - Scraping the Bottom of the Barrel, sessiontags: Java, sessionspeakers: Josh Bloch, Jeremy Manson, sessionabstract: How can they do it? How can Josh Bloch and Jeremy Manson keep coming up with such great programming puzzlers year after year? They can't! In this, the eighth installment of the perennial crowd pleaser, Click and Hack the Type-It brothers are truly scraping the bottom of the barrel. But the dregs they come up can still astonish, delight, and educate. So come to "Java Puzzlers,—Scraping the Bottom of the Barrel, have some fun, and learn to avoid the traps and pitfalls in the Java programming language., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/hQ6rx, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/hQ6rx, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: java-puzzlers, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wbp-3BJWsU8</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bctkt'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bpgoi</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 101</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 8, sessionproduct: Javascript, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Learning to Love JavaScript, sessiontags: JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Alex Russell, sessionabstract: JavaScript remains one of the most popular and important programming languages in history.  Web Developer and Chrome Engineer Alex Russell exposes the timeless strengths of the JavaScript language and why it is a vital part of the open web platform.  Come hear what's next for the JavaScript standard and how to get the most out of the new features coming soon in V8 and Chrome., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/P8T3K, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/P8T3K, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: learning-to-love-javascript, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=seX7jYI96GE</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bpgoi'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bqv8z</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 102</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, sessionroom: 5, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Make the Web Faster, sessionspeakers: Richard Rabbat, Josh Marantz, Håkon Wium Lie, sessionabstract: mod_pagespeed is an Apache module that web developers can use to automate web page performance optimizations. In this talk, we    examine how mod_pagespeed improves web page speed and reduces network bandwidth usage and describe the measured benefits on these pages. We then describe WebP, a new image format for the web, that reduces the bandwidth needs for images by 40% over JPEG for a comparable quality and demonstrate its support in Chrome and Opera., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/Q4pUz, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/Q4pUz, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: make-the-web-faster, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=30_AIEhar-I</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bqv8z'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bs9tc</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 103</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:30pm, sessionroom: 5, sessionproduct: General Engineering, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Programming Well with Others: Social Skills for Geeks, sessiontags: software engineering, teams, sessionspeakers: Brian Fitzpatrick, Ben Collins-Sussman, sessionabstract: Are languages, compilers, debuggers, and algorithms all you need to be a successful software engineer?  In a perfect world, those who produce the best code should be the most successful.  Unfortunately, we live in a world of imperfect people, and collaborating with others is at least as important as having great technical skills., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/TflGt, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/TflGt, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: programming-well-with-others, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q-7l8cnpI4k</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bs9tc'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/btodt</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 104</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 5, sessionproduct: Python, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: Python@Google, sessiontags: Python, App Engine, Web, Cloud, Dev Tools, Google APIs, Client Library, sessionspeakers: Wesley Chun, Guido van Rossum, sessionabstract: Python is one of the key languages at Google today. It runs on many our internal systems and shows up in many of our APIs. Some of the key contributors to the language are Googlers and continue to actively promote, use, and support the language. In this talk, we'll discuss Python's background &amp; history, discuss its philosophy, show you some syntax, and give some examples of what we use it for at Google., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/ejp4s, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/ejp4s, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: python-at-google, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KKQS8EDG1P4</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/btodt'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bjueu</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 105</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 3:45pm-4:45pm, sessionroom: 8, sessionproduct: Google Doodles, sessiontrack: Tech Talk, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: The Secrets of Google Pac-Man: A Game Show, sessiontags: Games, JavaScript, Doodles, sessionspeakers: Marcin Wichary, Ryan Germick, sessionabstract: Come participate in our game show-styled talk and learn the entertaining history of Google Pac-Man and other Google doodles through visual examples and code samples. Play along as we demonstrate the marriage of art and web technologies, talk about HTML5 techniques, discuss the user experience details, confess to bugs, and defend our design decisions., sessionurl: http://goo.gl/io/KQzVF, sessionshorturl: http://goo.gl/io/KQzVF, sessionhashtag: TechTalk, sessionslug: secrets-of-pac-man, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ttavBa4giPc</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bjueu'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bl8zb</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 106</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 6, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: App Engine Backends, sessiontags: App Engine, Backends, sessionspeakers: Justin Haugh, Greg Darke, sessionabstract: Applications written on App Engine can scale to amazing heights, but have strict limits on processing time, cpu, and memory usage.  App Engine Backends have few restrictions: they can use up to 1GB of memory, 4.8GHz of CPU, are individually addressable, and have no request deadlines.  We'll dive into the new kinds of programs that Backends enable and cover best practices., sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: app-engine-backends, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-kepYfCBg6w</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bl8zb'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bmnjo</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 107</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday May 10, sessiontime: 1:15pm-2:15pm, sessionroom: 9, sessionproduct: Android, sessiontrack: Android, sessionlevel: 301, sessiontitle: Android Open Accessory API and Development Kit (ADK), sessiontags: Android, Accessories, USB, sessionspeakers: Mike Lockwood, Erik Gilling, Jeff Brown, sessionabstract: You have always been able to connect an Android device to your computer, but until now there was no way for Android applications to interact with other hardware via USB.  In this talk we cover new support in Android 3.1 for USB input devices, as well as new APIs for applications to communicate with peripherals via USB.  The APIs support both Android powered devices that act as a conventional USB host, and non-host Android devices that communicates with a new class of USB hosts known as "Android USB Accessories".  Cool hardware is involved., sessionhashtag: Android, sessionslug: android-usb-accessories, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7szcpXf2rE</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bmnjo'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bo245</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 108</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, sessionroom: 10, sessionproduct: App Engine, sessiontrack: App Engine, sessionlevel: 201, sessiontitle: App Engine MapReduce, sessiontags: Map Reduce, sessionspeakers: Mike Aizatsky, sessionabstract: It is now possible to run full Map Reduce jobs on App Engine. This talk will include a short introduction into running Map Reduce jobs. After that we'll dive into practical and algorithmic aspects of generating various reports with Map Reduce., sessionhashtag: AppEngine, sessionslug: app-engine-mapreduce, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIxelKcyCC0</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/bo245'/>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/c0p7u</id>
		<updated>2011-05-16T23:33:42.238Z</updated>
		<category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/>
		<title type='text'>Row: 109</title>
		<content type='text'>sessiondate: Tuesday Oktober 18, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, sessionroom: 2, sessionproduct: Tasks API, sessiontrack: Google Apps, sessionlevel: 101, sessiontitle: Google Tasks API, sessiontags: Tasks, Tasks API, API, Enterprise, Interop, sessionspeakers: David Tattersall, Fabian Schlup, Andreas Signer, Nicolas Garnier, sessionabstract: The Google Tasks team have been hard at work and are proud to announce the Google Tasks API! We will introduce the new API and show you how to build awesome applications using it., sessionhashtag: GoogleApps, sessionslug: google-tasks-api, sessionyoutubeurl: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xlGdXDthL2w</content>
		<link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tmaLiaNqIWYYtuuhmIyG0uQ/od6/public/basic/c0p7u'/>
	</entry>
</feed>